{
    "subject": "resource/Naoum_Aronson",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Naoum Aronson (1872\u20131943) was a Russian-born sculptor who lived for most of his life in Paris.  He is known principally for his busts of important leaders, including Ludwig van Beethoven, Louis Pasteur, Leo Tolstoy, Grigori Rasputin, and Vladimir Lenin.Aronson was born to a Jewish family in what is now Latvia in 1872.  He studied art at the Vilna Art School before moving to Paris, where he would live for 50 years.  He maintained six galleries in Paris, but kept his prize pieces, including the bust of Rasputin, in his Montparnasse studio.  After the German invasion of France in 1940, he was forced to flee the country.  When he arrived in New York as a refugee in March, 1941 aboard the Serpa Pinto, he had little more than some photographs of the sculptures that he had left behind in France.  He died two years later in his Upper West Side studio at the age of 71.",
    "human_readable": "Naoum Aronson was a Russian-born sculptor who lived for most of his life in Paris and is known principally for his busts of important leaders.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.913976788520813,
            "question": "Was Naoum Aronson primarily a painter or sculptor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9030980467796326,
            "question": "Name one prominent leader whose bust was created by Naoum Aronson."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9010006785392761,
            "question": "Where did Naoum Aronson reside for the majority of his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8642423748970032,
            "question": "Where did Naoum Aronson spend most of his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8572713136672974,
            "question": "Where was Naoum Aronson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8134459853172302,
            "question": "What is Naoum Aronson most famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7979490756988525,
            "question": "Whose busts did Naoum Aronson create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7900316119194031,
            "question": "What type of artwork is Naoum Aronson known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7267195582389832,
            "question": "What nationality was Naoum Aronson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6804476976394653,
            "question": "Besides sculpting busts, what other types of art did Naoum Aronson create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Naoum Aronson was a Russian-born sculptor who lived for most of his life in Paris and is known principally for his busts of important leaders.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1621_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality was Naoum Aronson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1621_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of artwork is Naoum Aronson known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1621_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Whose busts did Naoum Aronson create?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1621_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1621_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple, meaning that Naoum Aronson was indeed a Russian-born sculptor who lived for most of his life in Paris and is known principally for his busts of important leaders."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Naoum Aronson being a Russian-born sculptor who lived most of his life in Paris, and that he is known principally for his busts of important leaders. This aligns with the statement given in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}